Hey guys
How are we doing today?
Hi
All right, well
So, I don't think it's a diet. It's not a dire. Um, I just, I'm sure I'll be able to get it fixed.
Hopefully it's not going to be expensive fix. There's something, but yeah, the bike is not
I'm charging. It kind of sucks, but it's still working. It's still working fine. Um,
so hopefully it's a good fix. I just don't, I just maybe just do some
Little quick fix with the charger. I ordered another one. We'll see if that works doesn't I'll return it
Then I'll take the bike to a
Repair place
Let's see how that goes
I'd love to have a quick fix for it
You have a neighbor that I built to take me down there
Maybe we'll work out some kind of payment for it, so we'll see
How's everyone doing get to see you guys I'm here with Lola right here. Miss Lola
Lola even slower
Hi, Doug
Okay, Lola Lola and tricks have been here
Hanging out with me
Hello guys
So hopefully it'll work. Oh
It's too big. It didn't seem like a bit, right? I'm not sure if it's even the right one
I have who knows. I don't think I've ever charged. I think I did charge it once
It's weird to start charging, but
We'll see what happens
We'll work again. How are you guys doing? I need to let my suit
I'll go through my lighter around.
The light, my cigarette.
Come on back.
Who fortunately there are you bike repair shops
Yeah, it was kind of a nightmare last night though
I was I went to the Whole Foods that I put my lock again. I put my lock in
The bike I forgot my lock was on so I'm driving the lock is now tangled up in the gears
I was able to ride home and stuff, but
You know
How's everyone doing I don't know how I got
I have my new 420
So we're gonna see if we can get this working again, we'll see I got Mike I got a core coming today
Hi guys. Yeah, it was kind of crazy last night, huh? It's like a little bit too much yesterday a little bit early
Yeah, but the bike fixed now I did it I got a well, I mean I was able to get you know
The lock is not the issue.
The lock is that the bike is not charging.
There is like a repair place I found.
Like locally, my neighbors might be able to see me
right over there.
He has a truck.
I don't know how much it will cost.
They're gonna be calling today, maybe.
I'll have a discussion with them.
It's still going, I mean, it's still working.
It's, now the battery gets lower and lower,
so I'm afraid it's not gonna start charging when it gets back.
But if anyone has any advice for you about,
if anybody had the same thing happen,
I'm sure it happens, it happens to them, you know,
if they have a limited,
they work, hopefully it's going to replace
the expensive battery or something.
So thank you guys for checking in
Yeah, I got a friend coming over today a little bit
For a little bit. Hey, babe. Oh
You change a directed outlet at least eight hours
Yeah, it's been you know overnight
It's plugged directly at the outlet. Yeah, it's a little power box. It says on when I plug it to the bike
There's no
Reactions at all. There's no it didn't say charging. There's no light goes on anywhere. It's just no reaction to it
So I don't know that I'll turn
Maybe another outlet or something
It I don't know what's going on with it. It sucks. Oh
Here we see
There are some videos maybe I can fix it this will go in
How's everyone doing in chat, yeah, it's been a little bit quiet had a few days
Thanks for the advice though. Look at the stringer. Oh, I didn't pin the link. Here's the linked hand
Here we go guys want to hang out
Lola
It's kind of 20 bucks for the new charger.
We'll see if that works.
It doesn't work.
I'll have to just reach from here and just hit there.
It might work though.
Hey, let's think positively.
What did I get to do charges?
Let's see if the charger works.
Would that be cool?
I'd make me happy.
We shall see.
How's everyone doing in chat?
Keep an eye out for FlowKey.
I do a FlowKey of reading still.
Let me make sure I do that reading for Flokey or Glokey
Yeah, I did get same-day delivery
Hi, Christine. Christine
The bike's okay, Christine
The bike's uh, well, I don't know if the bike's okay. I mean it's working fine
Um, it's just you know, it's not charging. I ordered a new charger for it
We'll see if that works if not
There's a little those little shops little repair places. I
Kind of maybe I'm thinking it's gonna be more difficult to fix than it will be I think it's maybe a quick fix
We'll see we should see
It's not you know
It was nice having a bike
There's ones on T move for like a hundred bucks
There's options other options
Hi guys, it's you though. Are you a friend coming over soon? Maybe I'll be clean a little bit chill
Yeah, they can be expensive I'd say maybe look at Timo his team who has that one's for like a hundred and twenty five hundred two bucks
They look decent
You look at the specifications
Or keep a bike
E-bike
Yeah, 169 170
$46 local
I mean, 46 bucks.
Oh, the way they went down the bike,
let me see the specification.
I mean, it looks pretty nice.
It says it's a GT electric bike.
It's locally.
It's a nice, powerful.
I mean, look they look decent
It's refurbished it looks like
It's $46
No, I think I think man is about $2,000. Yeah, so the $2,000 pie. Yeah, I
Just paid it and finished paying for it too
But I paid a couple hundred bucks for it
Yeah, they are expensive
Know I'm trying to Christine. I'm trying to but I can't help it. It's not charging. I mean it's big
Yeah, it's not charging
There was $500 one
You upgraded the gas. I don't know. I'd like I'd like to
reconsider that
But yeah, it's probably too dangerous for me
I don't know like what the wire it's like something because it works fine
It's like it's goes it works fine goes bad. It's still going. It's just not charging
So
Maybe they said it might be a fuse or something like there's a fuse energy replaced or
You know you would think that I don't know. I'm just hoping it's not too expensive to repair
Are we guys doing?
Even drink the beer I got a couple beers. I didn't drink them. It's like the sleep. I was kind of depressed
Don't like my things don't work and I was always I was afraid it would happen. I was like what if it's you know
I'm thinking I'm afraid of it and then they happen. He's that
Remus is a negative negative thoughts about it
But it's exactly what I was afraid probably if you use in the charger, yeah
Why you press because my bike and now it's he was so much fun. It was going so good and then
It's like now that there's always a problem with something now. I have to like figure out how to
Take it and it to pay for it to get repaired. In fact, it's a new charger doesn't work. I mean a new charger
So hopefully hopefully it is the charger like something in the charger. I'll just plug in another one over. Oh
Yeah, I like one thing's working. It's just I've had it for like months maybe
He'll be walking walk at this story now on and for a while
That's been doing that for years though
I'll be okay though see
Little bit right coming over
Chargers always go out do but remember don't plug it into extension cord always plug directly. Yeah, I think so
I think it is
And I thought way yesterday. I was like, oh, it wasn't on it. I think the outlet wasn't on and then I turned it on
Hi
That will turn me I'll try directly inside the outlet to directly. Hi guys
I'm gonna clean up a little bit.
Discussing ashtray.
You guys fighting?
Hi, guys.
Remember, it's Sunday.
We'll figure it out. They're gonna call me tomorrow,
probably, this, uh...
Place.
Okay, let's ask the pillow to the teeth
You got a lot of paperwork they can serve itself for
Another rich no for I'm like
I'm a kind of limbo, I don't you know
I'm I would say I'm
Oh my gosh
Okay, yeah, I mean I do work, you know consider this work the morning he man
Something is on fire
Okay
Hi guys
I'm okay
Yeah, how was it it was okay, it was okay. Yeah, I did hit on this hit, you know battle 10 days ago
It was okay. This one will be better this month
It was a little low because, you know, like, there were a lot of, it was lower than the first month.
There were a lot of people who, you know, have not renewed the membership because there were so many gifted memberships.
Now there have been a lot of gifted memberships this month.
Thank you. Memberships will help you out. Those memberships do help a lot.
I get about $3.
$3 that the membership is so if I get a hundred that's 300 bucks
It was less it was less
but then yeah, I haven't got me too many cash apps and
Yeah, the other super chats, too
If I have to wait I have to wait a few weeks. I have to wait a few weeks to
Bring in the wet the bike in or else they take it work. Yeah, three dollars three dollars membership. I
Think the first month I had about over a hundred
ad revenue
Yeah, the average I I don't have right and I got some videos that turned on
I really don't have it turned on on a lot of videos. I can you know later
Never a three dollars. Yeah, sure. I sure can
I went a little wild
This week with some some of the some of the food I'm slowing down
Hi, Lola
Oh, it's okay.
All right, thoughts on Jess, Jen.
I don't know who's Jess, Jen. I'm not sure.
Jess, is she the contact creator?
Is she in this chat? I'm not sure.
I don't know if I've heard of Jess, Jen.
I know of, like, uh...
I've heard of different people. I've never heard of Jess, Jen.
Somebody got a membership yesterday.
I did do it in a membership yesterday.
Blame it on Katie or something. Hey summer
Why?
Hey kitty cats, blame it on Katie or something like that
And she supposedly is some kind of like styrox for cover styrox fully. Oh, they know who she is
She's donated, okay
Well just I would say she's a thank you. She's a great person. She's
Part of IP to it is LD sister. Okay
Yeah, I don't think I met her you know LD was on the show last night for a little bit
You know look
seeing Duke and stuff his dog
All right. Hi K caps
Hey
Hi guys
Hi, it's nice to see everyone gonna come in getting along. Hi, babe. Hi babes
Hi Jenna, oh here Jenna, how are you? Good beautiful neighbor. I miss you too
Yeah, yeah, if you know, oh, the cats are good cats are good
Yeah, if you know any place that you don't place that repairs e-bikes
because
My bike's not charging. I don't know
It's not charging Lola
Lola, thank you so much.
Yes, it's not charging.
I ordered a new charger.
Thank you, Jenna.
I ordered a new charger and I'll see if that works today.
But if not, it's just like my bike's not charging.
I don't know if it's easy to fix or not.
Thank you so much.
Rudy's good.
Let's see if I can grab Rudy.
Rudy here, right here.
Hi, Rudy.
Hi, Mr. Roode.
Can I come over here?
What?
Oh.
We don't have a cat or a husband let's say David Beckham. I don't know. I'm money
Yeah, I think it's a battery meant I'll check the charger the connection it seems kind of loose
I don't know it might be a damaged battery and I might the battery seems to be working fine
It seems to be working, you know, or the battery management system. Yeah
Are you there money for 20?
I don't think you can hear me
Yeah
So I'll have a look at this
How are you?
Yeah, yeah, I hear you I was gonna tell you if you bought the bike from a shop
That's automatically supposed to be covered the batteries bring that shit into
But I bought it, you know, I bought it. I bought it you use or you know, it's somebody else
I'm not it wasn't bought recently from a shop is you know, so
Yeah, that place is around here that that do a e-bike repair, so so hopefully it's not
Anything bring it somewhere let them check it out. So I don't want any bikes and I had a bunch of them
How about your own
Had this one
Now I got this one guys no more batteries
Hey
Yeah
Well, yeah, you know cheap batteries though. He's just me frying out. They don't last long
Yeah, I guess like but they can replace them right or they are they were expensive to places that replace and stuff or
You might have to release it, but they don't want to express it
Okay, okay tangled part from the lock it it yeah
Just by a motorcycle yeah, well, yeah quite a forward one yet, so maybe in the future
Yeah, I think it might be the charging port
Okay money, thank you for the advice
See if I can get it best, but yeah, I need to get my driver's license fixed again, too
No, they let me the lock got tangled in it, but that's that's like the least of the problem
It's a charging issue the law the lock I can yeah, I can you know that could be cut out pretty easily
Yep, well we're kind of how are you doing today guys you do some readings
Hang out
Yeah, I don't know for me
I will Christine. Thank you
This is like there's so much I can do. It's like all I can pretty much do is you know plug it in there
See if it charges. I mean, that's that's
Only I don't know if there's any
Buttons or anything
Yeah, it did it did nothing. I could nothing got jammed up in the wheels
It was I was able to like untangle it and just tie it around one of the wheels and it wrote it wrote fine
So I know that was kind of
Hey, babe, it's Lola Lola such a good cat
Okay, I'll have a look at it. No, I want to get this fixed
It's not like I can open up the carriage inside of it, so I mean I
Hope I'm doing something wrong
We'll have to charge Archer down.
We'll figure it out. Hey guys, how are we doing today? So let's see. How do we got cards for us?
Cards for us.
What do we got for us this morning? Oh seven of cups.
Seven of cups is there's like a lot of options and there's so many you know
A few of the cubs might have poison in them few of the cubs might have something you really want
You know, you're like, which one should I take? We know you want to avoid the poison?
Here's your day off. Yeah, so the seven of cups that shows that there's a lot of options maybe some confusion
You need to find what you like the most focus on that cup, you know
And then go for it, but it says seven of cups the seven of cups ask you to take inspiration from Alice and the dream
Allow your imagination to wander the age you may can be a powerful act of manifestation and form the framework for your future goals and
Actions tap into your intuition and let your mind wander who knows what wonderful adventures or dreams will take you to
Okay
Those we got for us
Emperors all the all the cards in the deck and the emperor he has this compassion
You know because he was able to always like you know the Queen of Hearts was a little bit off with their heads
And she was a little a little while back to your documents. Okay, Christine, but yeah, we got the emperor
He's gonna be a good man
someone that
Yeah, like so it's that a reason and he's a good ruler. It's a good ruler
So I don't know if you've got this man in your life or you're just coming into the energy yourself
You might be a good ruler right over your kingdom. We all have our own kingdoms
Okay, we got another seven we get the seven of flowers those seven of wands, okay
Seven of wands says that you've been
On the defense about something
Holding your ground depending what you have what you love my book
Just have the book
Okay
We got seven seven that could be also relevant so the seven of flowers says
Seven of flowers advise you to be defensive your facing challenges and rivalry now isn't the time to for a politeness or backing down
Keep your shoulders squared hold on your ground and remember you earn your place in the garden. Okay?
So hold your ground hold your ground don't let anyone push you around
It's that you got your maybe under attack. You got the seven of cups
You get that one
Thank you, man. That's good. I got ideas. I have to charge her down in the outlet
To be here between 10 to 10 and two they said the I got it same day delivery
So let's have some advice with my advice for everybody
Chariot just keep going forward keep moving forward. You have four momentum. You got a vehicle, maybe
Yeah, I don't know. Well mine is working, but hopefully you have a vehicle or
Even your body's a vehicle. He's got to keep moving forward. I see victory
Let's the chariot the chariot it's that forward momentum for movement and
Keep going keep going
Okay
Little stops along the way sometimes people's cars have to go in the shop for a few days, you know, it's like, you know, it's expensive. It's inconvenient
but
Things can be fixed things can be things to be
Made to work again, right? So well, there's some tricks. How are we doing guys? We're having a great day
It'll be a little bit. It'll be a better day. I'll be a better day
You know, I have faith that
Faith that everything will work out
Documents so yeah, I gotta clean the book. I got this cleaned up a little bit
Also wonderland, yep, pretty cool deck love the villains deck of the Alice deck
I'm really cool Dex. I had a pretty good dinner last night. I had potatoes. I had some
pasta salad. I still have a burger to eat today. It's a turkey burger. I took it up to eat this one.
Hi Lola. Lola. My little show girl.
You love to cuddle, huh? You love to cuddle?
Mmm, what kiss is it? You love to kiss and cuddle?
I... I... it's very calm.
Oh
The tricks
Like he has been draining up with these days a lot of energy pulls
exchange yeah
Just get draining, huh?
People don't realize there is like a big energy exchange in terror and terror and it's like, you know
I feel the energy I go into other people's energy
And yeah, it can be taxing. Hi all those just rolling around on my belly
How's everybody else doing with anything going on in the YouTube world?
I haven't seen that much. I know we had Carl on last night. I might have fallen asleep again. Not sure. Oh
Lola. I think I turned off the stream on time.
Beautiful kitty cat.
Yeah. The tracking people, yeah.
But I just try to be myself as like, you know, so it doesn't get
Not not like putting on a mask, you know
Which would be exhausting and draining
You're comfortable
There's a lot of energy people like to just let's put into maintaining a mask
Which it says take a lot of energy because then the mask will slip because no one can wear a mask for that long
And so and everyone kind of does wear a mask
But
Some masks are very different from what the person is
My mask is basically just
You know
I want tv so smile a little bit
Yeah, oh, she's so comfy
Hi
Oh
Can you come over and say hi to you?
I was completely different person last night.
I know, it was the, you know, it seemed to be four weeks,
you know, how nice he was and stuff last night,
but then he was like, he's like,
oh, everyone told him to come over to my chat right now.
I'm gonna be live, but this is good, it's fine.
And he's like, he's like, oh, I think I want He-Man.
I want, you know, I want He-Man on Jamie's Cowboys
and my shit, I was like, well, I know.
You know, he wants my, he wants my mods,
It's okay. It's okay Carl. Your meds made you knock out last night. See
Uh, it sounds late night lives. Yeah, I wasn't away too late. I wasn't it wasn't away too late last night, right?
I bought another couple beers. I didn't drink them
Hi
He waked out and beat us.
What happened?
Oh, he did?
Yeah.
Well, I just woke up at 10.
I woke up earlier this morning.
I was off for a few minutes.
There's nobody really here, though, so.
Oh, no, bitch.
He might knock you out.
Yeah, Carl was good afternoon sassy. Yeah, Carl was a little bit weird last night, huh?
Hey nice guy, but I just heard me enough. I've heard him talk about talk about me at B to say, oh
He's like criticized my
How I read you know my tarot
So he turned evil last night. Was he the evil guy or he was the nice guy?
Not sure.
He's real mean I'm beat his panel. Yeah, I can see he's like not he's like smiling, but he's like
Usually
He was smiling
But there's just something there I can tell thank you
Yeah, thank you. Oh my god, he's a lot
Chew chew chew chew
Yeah, we will do have a deep mouth.
How are we doing guys?
Yeah, so we'll see what happens today
Morning pot hawk is
Yeah, you just seem like he was like really nice, but you know I've heard stories about
He's into black magic, or yeah, you've heard that sassy
And he was like looking into my eye. He was being very like, you know, I was and I avoided looking into his eyes because
He's gonna see he's trying to like pull you in
So yeah, I have heard he does bell casting maybe some black magic and stuff from the you know black magic is
There were a lot of black magic in witchcraft. It really sacrificed animals. Oh my god. I hope that's not true either
That's really I
Don't think it's effective either. I don't think that it sacrificed the animals of any kind of great effects. It's just
unnecessary cruelty and
I hope I'll ask him about that right around.
Yeah I mean it's like magic it's like you know black magic what's that gonna have it's gonna
have a lot of heat as it's as the power behind it's gonna have a lot of negativity
It's painful, painful energies, they're cursing, hating, pouring negative energy to that.
You pour that out, you're going to get some really negative things happening to you.
This is basically just pouring it onto yourself.
I don't know he's like the people like that are they he like once
He's like he's frustrated. He wants to have sex with them or I
Don't know
I'm gonna
They want to lay down a little bit longer
See if my friend comes in. Yeah, I feel it on a percent right now. Hopefully the bike will be fixed. We'll see
I'll give you updates. Love you guys
Love you guys.